[
  {
    "Question": "Are you an introvert or an extrovert?",
    "LeftAnswer": "Introvert",
    "RightAnswer": "Extrovert",
    "LeftPoints": 20,
    "RightPoints": 10
  },

  {
    "Question": "Do you like warm or cold colors?",
    "LeftAnswer": "Warm",
    "RightAnswer": "Cold",
    "LeftPoints": 10,
    "RightPoints": 20
  },

  {
    "Question": "Are you a night owl or a morning owl?\", \"Night Owl",
    "LeftAnswer": "Night Owl",
    "RightAnswer": "Morning Owl",
    "LeftPoints": 40,
    "RightPoints": 5
  },

  {
    "Question": "Do you like Math/Sciences or English/History/Arts?\", \"Math/Sciences\", \"English/History/Arts",
    "LeftAnswer": "Math/Sciences",
    "RightAnswer": "English/History/Arts",
    "LeftPoints": 5,
    "RightPoints": 5
  },

  {
    "Question": "Do you procrastinate your work?",
    "LeftAnswer": "Yes",
    "RightAnswer": "No",
    "LeftPoints": 30,
    "RightPoints": 5
  },

  {
    "Question": "How long do you spend on the computer everyday?",
    "LeftAnswer": "Less than an hour",
    "RightAnswer": "More than an hour",
    "LeftPoints": 5,
    "RightPoints": 40
  },

  {
    "Question": "Do you like traveling?",
    "LeftAnswer": "Yes",
    "RightAnswer": "No",
    "LeftPoints": 5,
    "RightPoints": 25
  },

  {
    "Question": "Do you clean your room?",
    "LeftAnswer": "Yes",
    "RightAnswer": "No",
    "LeftPoints": 10,
    "RightPoints": 20
  },

  {
    "Question": "Do you like school?",
    "LeftAnswer": "Yes",
    "RightAnswer": "No",
    "LeftPoints": 0,
    "RightPoints": 30
  },

  {
    "Question": "Do you prefer the Summer/Spring or Winter/Fall",
    "LeftAnswer": "Summer/Spring",
    "RightAnswer": "Winter/Fall",
    "LeftPoints": 5,
    "RightPoints": 5
  }
]